you guys are welcome to the another video we will see what is up here to pure original means
so I we have a anti-verse dot exe let me execute this is a renaissance administrator so now
we got a sponsor right so let me let me remove this okay so let me interact with that
and let me go to the come and elevate dash SBC sorry elevate SPC dash exe okay SBC okay
the night was asking for a listener so don't worry about that this topic we will see this
in a pure legislation section early or now I need to explain the peer to peer so that I
is explaining this I am choosing this so it was created a econ a pipe command I will explain
what is a pipe and all the things in a upcoming this okay so here you can find there is
a there is a two windows machine of there right to to dig us there so here you can see
the deconstructure so it was pointing to the cobalt sink this is the cobalt side and there
is a first anti-verse dot exe and another one we got a one nine two zero as a bit right
and let me interact with this first let me do the PS command and I will do the PS command
for this also will get a few minutes so the basic theory is when you are executing
any PS command from this console like four three seven six speed okay four three seven six
the anti-verse dot exe it will directly executed in the in the anti-verse dot exe a parallel
okay from this okay so when you are executing any command in one nine two zero okay so
first of all it will go it will go to the first anti-verse dot exe and the anti-verse dot
exe sent to the another Rendial 30 dot exe and it will execute that and the Rendial 30 dot
exe will send the results back to the user and this user will send the result back to
the cobalt sake okay so the normal listener it will directly send the results to the cobalt
sake or it will directly execute the command but peer to peer listener first of all the
command will go to the first listener and then it will be go to the second listener and it
will be execute that okay so that way you can see the connection from this to the first
anti-verse dot exe communicating the cobalt sake directly the next payload I mean the Rendial
30 dot exe communicating from the anti-verse dot exe right there is a one in between
there is one channel will be there right the anti-verse dot exe okay so in between there
is a connection okay so when you are when you are executing any command by interacting
this be gone okay so if you are giving the shell I have I pick on fake so how this command
will execute by like so first of all this is a cobalt sake it will go to the first listener
and then it will be send it to the second listener okay this is how the peer to peer listener
will work okay or we will wait for this command results and we will hop off this video and
we will continue our discussion in the next section okay will wait for result so you can
see the IP of the machine was 18.34 that gives the listener yeah we will hop off this video
and we will continue our discussion next section see you guys bye bye.